//Display question and choices in browser
const quizQuestions = [
    {
        question : "In the comics, who is Red's starting Pokemon?", //pokemon
        imgSrc : "../images/pikachu.gif",
        choices: ["Clefairy","Pikachu","Bulbasaur","Eevee"],
        correctAnswer: "Clefairy"
    },
    {
        question : "What game did Mario first appear in?", //mario
        imgSrc : "../images/mario.gif",
        choices: ["Super Mario Bros","Donkey Kong","Legend of Zelda", "Pong"],
        correctAnswer: "Donkey Kong"
    },
    {
        question : "How many timelines are in the Legend of Zelda series?", //loz
        imgSrc : "../images/link-loz.gif",
        choices: ["Two", "Three", "Four", "One"],
        correctAnswer: "Three"
    },
    {
        question : "Who is the current Lich King?", //wow
        imgSrc : "../images/lichking.gif",
        choices: ["Arthas Menethil", "Bolvar Fordragon","Sylvanas Windrunner","Thrall"],
        correctAnswer: "Bolvar Fordragon"
    },
    {
        question : "Who is the protagonist of the Mass Effect trilogy?", //mass effect
        imgSrc : "../images/mass-effectgif.gif",
        choices: ["Captain Shepard","Officer Shepard","John Shepard","Commander Shepard"],
        correctAnswer:"Commander Shepard"
    },
    {
        question : "What US city does Deus Ex:Humant Revolution start in?", //de:hr
        imgSrc : "../images/adamjensen.gif",
        choices: ["Hong Kong","Detroit","New York","Seattle"],
        correctAnswer: "Seattle"
    },
    {
        question : "Which Final Fantasy character has appeared in every numbered FF game?",
        imgSrc : "../images/cloud-seph.gif", //final fantasy
        choices: ["Cid", "Sid", "Syd","Cloud"],
        correctAnswer: "Cid"
    },
    {
        question : "When was the first Super Smash Bros released?",
        imgSrc : "../images/smash-bros.gif", //smash bros
        choices: ["1998", "2002", "1997", "1999"],
        correctAnswer: "1999"
    },
    {
        question : "What name did the protaginists call their team?",
        imgSrc : "../images/persona-5.gif", //persona
        choices: ["The Crew","The Thieves", "The Phantom Thieves", "The Heart Seekers"],
        correctAnswer: "The Phantom Thieves"
    },
    {
        question : "In most Silent Hill games there is a 'joke' ending. What is it called?",
        imgSrc : "../images/robbie-silenthill.gif", //silent hill
        choices: ["The Joke Ending", "The Cat Ending", "The Dog Ending", "The Funny Ending"],
        correctAnswer: "The Dog Ending"
    },
    {
        question : "BONUS QUESTION): Is the Legend of Zelda series older, or younger than Joe?",
        imgSrc : "../images/robbie-silenthill.gif", //bonus question
        choices: ["Zelda is Older", "Joe is Older", "Both are equally sweet summer children"],
        correctAnswer: "Joe is Older"
    },
    
];